const STORE = [
    {
      question: "What are the different lands throughout the main part of Disneyland?",
      answers: [
        'Adventureland, Fantasyland, Frontierland, Tomorrowland',
        'Mainstreet, The Hub, The Disneyland Castle, Mickeys Parking structure',
        'Adventureworld, Fantasyworld, Frontierworld, Tomorrowworld',
        'EPCOT, Animal Kingdom, Hollywood Studios, Magic Kingdom'
        
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Adventureland, Fantasyland, Frontierland, Tomorrowland',
      //icon: 'image of icon',
      //alt: 'description of icon'
    },

    {
        question: "What was Mickey's first cartoon?",
        answers: [
          'Fantasia',
          'Steamboat Willie',
          'Silly Symphony',
          'Brave Little Tailor'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: 'Steamboat Willie',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },

      {
        question: "In Fantasia, Dance of the Hours, what is the Hippo's name?",
        answers: [
          'Helena Hippo',
          'Hyacinth Hippo',
          'Helga Hippo',
          'Henrietta Hippa'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: 'Hyacinth Hippo',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },

      {
        question: 'The Mark XLII Autonomous Prehensile Propulsion armor is also known as...?',
        answers: [
          'The Hulkbuster',
          'The Bleeding Edge Armor',
          'The Prodigal Son',
          'The Nanotech Armor'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: 'The Prodigal Son',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },

      {
        question: 'Which of the following actors is credited for the most Disney animated voices?',
        answers: [
          'Alan Tudyk',
          'Tara Strong',
          'Mark Hamill',
          'Jim Cummings'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: 'Jim Cummings',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },

      {
        question: 'Which of the following is the most permiere Disney dining experience?',
        answers: [
          "Cinderella's Castle",
          'Club 33',
          '21 Royal',
          'Cafe Orleans'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: '21 Royal',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },

      {
        question: 'Today, there is Star Wars land, but what Imagineering concept was supposed to go there, but never did?',
        answers: [
          'Disney SEA',
          'Marvel Land',
          'Fantasyland Expansion',
          'Discovery Bay'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: 'Discovery Bay',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },

      {
        question: 'What were the original names of the Hyenas in The Lion King?',
        answers: [
          'Shenzi, Banzai, Ed',
          'Shenzi, Kamari, Azizi',
          'Shenzi Marie Predatora Veldetta Jacquelina Hyena, Kovu, Kion',
          'Shenzi, Zazu, Ahadi'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: 'Shenzi, Kamari, Azizi',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },

      {
        question: 'In what year did the Axiom begin its return to Earth after being away for 700 years after the start of Operation Cleanup?',
        answers: [
          '2905',
          '2705',
          '2805',
          '3005'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: '2805',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },

      {
        question: 'Which Disney Princess has the fewest amount of lines?',
        answers: [
          'Jasmine',
          'Cinderella',
          'Snow White',
          'Aurora'
          
          ],
        correctAnswer: 'Aurora',
        //icon: 'image of icon',
        //alt: 'description of icon'
      },]